Wait,
self-serving versus interesting.
You are not understanding.
Let me explain,
every time we try to be accepted,
it seems that we are more interested than interesting.
Being pretty honest,
man,
I'm tired of asking people for opportunities,
I'm tired of talking,
brother.
Notice me.
I'm going to wear a nice outfit to spend saliva with you,
so you can judge my appearance and not my creative ability.
I got tired, dear.
There.
Who has the ball this time?
It's the guy who's going to give you the opportunity or not,
bro,
how do we break that?
How do we get this grid off?
He arrives.
I've tried everyone's attention.
We need to create our own box.
Learn to tell stories and the stories will connect customers,
people,
brands,
companies and everything you can imagine.
And that's exactly what I'm doing here.
When we start to be more interesting and less interested,
guess what,
you don't go to the customer,
it's the customer that goes to you,
and when people see value in you,
guess what attracts us because I'm going to
create something from a conventional model,
you can start a project with real,
go physical,
go digital,
do digital,
do physical digital,
do physical physical only,
that's it just a matter of format.
We don't have to separate one thing from the other,
because it's the same thing.
It's on,
no matter the connection channel.
Yes,
what do you generate because you don't do that in your business.
Today is fifty-seven.
Then, Juninho guys,
I'm going to set up an Instagram,
follow us there,
we don't follow you there,
follow me there,
follow me there, huh?
There guys Juninho is from Instagram,
it's there in the description of the video bro
it's over man how are you
make another sip there with you good thing I'm in the engine without rushing.
Dude, bro,
I came here to leave a greenhouse bro it's crowded the
store brother bora brother and now I'm going there to see Sebas,
bro.
I put him on the train.
Matthew.
My brother is in a relationship again,
he meets the guys,
we are going to become Brother,
so I'm already taking my break.
Apparently,
everything is fine.
I wanted to tell you 1 piece of news now.
Yes, bro,
we're with you until tomorrow.
Try to leave that pressure,
get up off that thing,
twist and you be Better.